This stuff is excellent!
I have come all the way from Lanka
in search of a land just like this.
This place yields gold.
Hey, Varada.
This village is mine from now on.
My permission is mandatory for anyone
who wants to go or come.
With the Lord as my witness.
Hello?
Greetings.
The situation in the orphanage is bad.
The children…
aren't receiving proper meals
due to this situation.
Not here, look over there.
Mr. Murthy, please ensure
the kids are served properly.
Ensure everyone eats
to their full. Got it?
Eat well, my boy.
This news must be highlighted prominently.
All hail Kamalakar,
the generous food provider!
We are unable to pay
for their daily needs.
We don't have…
any sponsors.
I'm adopting these six academically
gifted children through my company.
You're a great man.
Thank you.
Mr. Murthy and the children
from the orphanage are here.
Did ma'am send ₹ 10 lakhs cash?
-Yes, sir.
-Send that cash in. Send those people out.
Okay, sir.
We have not received any aid
from you in a long time.
If you could show us some mercy…
Why are humans like this?
One man tricked us
with a false promise of food.
Another gave us
a false assurance of sponsorship.
I believed he'd really sponsor my studies.
I hoped to study well and find a good job,
and support other kids
like us in their studies.
Those who visit us here
are nothing but thieves.
They're just using us for their gains.
No, buddy. You can't talk
about our family members like that.
"India is my country.
All Indians are my brothers and sisters."
is the pledge we take every day.
What does it mean?
This country is our family.
Every citizen of this country
are our family members.
Relying on family when necessary
is completely fine, dude.
So, all of you just want
to study well. Is that it?
With our family’s support,
I will educate you.
But how?
-Dad. I want that balloon.
-Why a balloon? It'll just pop.
Even food gets digested, sir.
Does that mean we stop eating?
Good logic, Dad.
I really want this balloon.
How much?
You are like my family, sir.
You need not pay.
Since you see me as family,
give me one more.
Off you go.
Didn't I warn you
that the balloon would pop…!
Mr. Murthy, there's a money order for you.
To us?
Hey, eat till you're full.
Hey, Ram.
I'll join you in helping
educate all our friends.
Why deal with all this? Just study well.
It's tough for me to study, man.
What interests you then?
-What do you want, dear?
-Is Mr. Mahendra home, ma'am?
I need to hand over this parcel to him.
I'm his wife. You can give it to me.
If you're his wife,
then who’s the person in these photos?
Sister…
You gave ₹ 10 lakhs in cash, correct?
I overheard him saying
he'd give it to her.
Who the hell is she?
Did you also give those ₹ 10 lakhs to her?
Don't hit me.
They are in the locker above.
Burglaries in high-profile homes continue!
Who is this Robin Hood
who targets the wealthy,
loots heavily, and goes on a
spree of robberies?
Someone is executing his masterplan
and robbing off the whole lot
and these TV channels
are rapping out his feats!
It might be a joke to you,
but we’re burning inside!
Sir! Your BP is shooting up.
Please calm down.
Those waiting outside aren’t here
to cry over their own losses.
They heard about the burglary
at my business partner Agarwal’s home,
and came to console me.
How does it matter whose house
gets targeted among us both?
I feel embarrassed
to call myself the Home Minister.
I don’t care what you'll do
or who you'll get rid of!
The case needs to be solved.
And the thief needs to be caught.
Victor Varghese.
Who is he?
A wild dog.
He only trusts his instincts.
Zero unsolved cases.
Consider the case is solved, sir.
Victor is on it.
What happened?
We woke up at 5 in the morning
for Lakshmi pooja today.
We wanted to keep gold in the pooja room,
We cut the CCTV feed to keep
security away from looking it.
Out of nowhere, a man
with an N-95 mask showed up, sir.
He took off everything he could grab.
-How does he look like?
-Pretty average, sir.
Listen dear,
he didn't ask about you.
That guy is six feet tall.
He had an almost six-pack physique.
He looked very smart.
What is this, dear?
Stop! We must tell the truth
to cops and doctors.
Any clue about his body language?
His eyes were classy,
and his body language screamed mass!
I couldn't see his lips
because of the mask,
-but from his walking style…
-Hey, note all this down.
Sir!
You've got to grab him, sir!
What the hell is this?
The bike seen near
Agarwal’s house this morning
was just spotted at Sona Bazaar, sir.
I need information on the kingpin
who handles illegal gold trade
in bulk in these areas immediately.
Seth Chaman Lal
is the kingpin of that market.
Sir, the deal won't take place
there once we go.
After the heist at Agarwal's house
at early morning 5 a.m.,
he's now casually going
to Sona Bazaar.
Do you understand his attitude, sir?
Get the interrogation room ready.
You've got a dinner date
with that thief tonight.
Should I bring the bag, Seth?
Not today, Johnny.
I suspect the police are closing in on us.
The police?!
Let's not take any risks, Johnny.
Police are around us.
We have no idea how many are there.
Seth said not to bring the bag today.
Hey!
They must be the criminals. Move!
Open the door.
Break the door.
You said you don't know
how many they are and where they are.
13 members in altogether.
They're on duty
but clearly not into dieting.
Their bellies are
spilling out of their shirts.
It'll take them ten minutes
to figure out that we're not connected.
That’s plenty of time to not just swap
the gold, but the whole shop!
How did you figure out
the police would be here?
Whether they come or not,
if we prepare for their arrival,
there won't be a problem
even if they come.
Something happened here.
Speak the truth, Chaman Lal.
Sir, I am not Chaman Lal, I’m Pyare Lal,
See the board for yourself.
Hey! Who put Chaman Lal’s name
on my board?
Sir!
Sir.
This guy's playing the game too well.
Now. I'll show him my game.
-Bharat.
-Sir.
I need all the CCTV footage
from this area immediately.
Okay, sir.
-Hello!
-The interrogation room is ready.
-Have you caught the thief?
-Sir got caught up!
When the hunter makes a stupid face
The deer hoodwinked him
The little fish kicked
The blind crane in the back
India is my country
He uses the backdoor for his entry
Breaks every lock in sight
Clearing safes out overnight
With the Rich folks' balance
He plays PUBG!
A bridge between slums &amp; mansions
He stands firm, hot as fire
Go rob, rob, rob, Robinhood!
Ram, I found a job for you.
Join if you like it.
Those hoarding black cash
Are his "mummy-daddies"
Like income tax raids
He empties their vaults day in and out
He snatches gold
Without even the chain finding out
He's chill as a beer
While pulling off a heist
Stop!
Are you an Arab?
No.
Then, why are you
wearing an Arab costume?
-Is she a Punjabi?
-No.
I'm here.
Then why is she
wearing a Punjabi dress?
Logical!
Goddess Lakshmi Devi’s true fanboy
He lifts fortunes like a toy
A bandit with a brand new style
Sinking ships with a cheeky smile
No blood, no breed— just his name
A walking ATM for the poor in pain
A rich man today
Gets his notice
When bad time strikes
He's like the sun
Drinking the ocean dry
Then fills the clouds
And showers the land with raindrops
A musician who pinches
And then sings lullaby
A magician who blindfolds everyone
Hey rob, rob, rob, Robinhood!
Go rob, rob, rob, Robinhood!
He's the scammer who's been trending
all over the news and social media lately.
Where's the respect, dude?
He's our uncle.
Let me go and meet him.
Catch the bloody bugger. Move!
The locker room is fully blurred.
-Is he there?
-That's why it is still blurred, sir.
To break through that door…
He'll need his ancestors' help!
There's no way to escape.
He's trapped!
-Got you, Robinhood!
-Ram!
He's here to capture Robinhood.
-He's our special officer.
-Special officer?
Darn!
Missed him again!
Who the hell is he?
He was the first person
to file a case on Robinhood, sir.
Son of stock broker Ramalingeshwar Rao.
Sir, there was a robbery at our house.
Everything my dad earned was lost.
My Dad is no more, sir.
Still no information
on that robber, right?
I'm so sorry, Ram.
We're still trying.
I will definitely catch the one
who tore my family apart.
This is just a job for you, sir.
For me, it's a mission.
A mission!
Sir, 20 to 30 people who showed up
as technicians are running away.
-Did you catch anyone?
-When asked, one of them said
that they were told to show up
in this costume for a movie shoot, sir.
He's shifting our focus every time,
and escaping.
Wherever he escapes to…
I'll catch him for sure.
You bugger!
You think you're a hero, huh?
Do you really think
you’ll catch him before I do?
This is just a job for you. For me,
it's a mission. I'll catch him for sure.
If I find you in this case again,
or even cross paths with you,
I'll arrest you and declare you as
Robinhood and close the case.
Yes, sir!
I'm Robinhood.
From today my name is Robinhood.
Go ahead. Arrest me.
-I'll shoot if I hear a word from you.
-Sure. Go ahead. Shoot.
Listen to me. Don't get yourself
in trouble. Please, go away.
Please.
Sharif.
I want to be informed of
all his movements from here on.
When someone whom you helped,
faces hardship,
standing by them in support
is the true path of righteousness.
Wow! What a great escape!
I wondered why you wanted me
to create a family photo.
But today, it really came in handy, man.
Hey, what's wrong?
When I was a helpless kid on the streets,
an old man brought me here
and left me in his care.
Since then, he's been my everything.
The police have caught up with me today.
They'll get to him tomorrow.
If that happens, the orphanage kids
will all be treated like thieves.
I've used up
the only lifeline I had, dude.
I'm not taking any chances.
I'll give Robinhood rest from today,
and start a regular job from tomorrow.
Who's going to give you
a job on such short notice?
Ground breaking achievement.
Indian origin AV Pharmas'
medical cannabis-based
oral cancer cure
is earning global praise.
The Indian Medical Council has issued
a license to start a second unit in India.
By such, congratulating AV Pharmaceutical
company and MD Abhinav Vasudev.
-Good morning, sir.
-Pretty heavy breeze today, eh?
-Hey! Suit looks awesome.
-Thank you. Means a lot coming from you.
You don’t fit to that suit.
Go change it!
You vile creature!
You set up your company here
because they denied permission in India.
Today, they're literally begging you
to set up one in India.
You're an achiever, buddy!
Hey! You shouldn't be
drinking coffee at this time, dude!
Champagne!
-Not in the mood, buddy.
-What's wrong?
-My daughter is hurt.
-But why?
So, if you could all join me
in congratulating
the wonderful efforts of our MD
Mr. Abhinav Vasudev.
And his daughter…
Miss…
Miss… uh…
What's her name?
I don't know.
I know her as AV's daughter.
Mr. Abhinav Vasudev's daughter.
Darling, he's an Amnesia patient.
He doesn't even remember his wife's name.
He remembers your name, Dad.
Do you know the reason why kids
of famous personalities
don't become famous themselves, Dad?
It's not because they lack talent.
It's because no
one recognizes their talent.
To grow…
I must go away from you.
-Why hold on to just an incident?
-It's not about just one, Dad!
I've been facing this since childhood.
I studied hard and took the entrance test
for admission to my favorite school.
When I went to the principal's room
excitedly for exam results…
My scores are irrelevant. She gave me
admission just because I’m your daughter.
You know how successful the first project
I led in our company.
We received appreciation letters
from our competitor companies.
You probably thought I was outgrowing you.
My cabin stayed,
but not my work.
-No. Don't do this.
-What?
-Are you getting emotional?
-While searching for talent outside,
if we forget the talent
under our own roof, won't it hurt, sir?
Listening to that,
tears welled up in my eyes.
Having talent is one thing,
assuming you have it is another.
There's another angle to this story.
Reading her answers
after she studied hard,
the teacher had a seizure
and collapsed.
The principal rejected the admission
after admitting him in hospital.
To avoid his daughter being disappointed,
he bought the seat.
You bribed her?
What?!
The company’s value
went down 15 percent within a week!
Do you know how much it costs?
Dad! You know what?
Our competitor companies sent me
appreciation letters for my project.
Why won't they, when they are the ones
benefitting.
Are you proud of me, Dad?
Uncle?
Why do you look so dull
in such a happy moment?
-I've got a headache, dear.
-Headache, but why?
Do you know how
a headache comes, dear?
It comes directly to the head, right?
You're right!
No, sir. Don't.
Why are you crying again this time?
Didn't you say
the headache comes to the head?
Listening to that…
-tears in my eyes--
-welled up in your eyes?
-Exactly, sir. Did it happen to you, too?
-Bloody idiot!
Stop it, dude!
I'm already stressed
that she's going to India.
To India?
What twist is this?
Fish can't survive without water,
and I can't stay
where I'm not valued, Jyothi.
Someone is calling you
continuously, ma'am.
If they're calling so many times,
it means someone thinks I'm important.
Am I speaking to
Pavitra's daughter?
-Who's this?
-I'm your aunt, dear.
I'm calling from Rudrakonda.
Your grandfather is very ill.
He's been asking to see you.
Our family is waiting for your arrival.
You'll come, right?
What?!
Have you gone nuts?
After your mom and I moved to Australia,
they literally treated us
like we didn't exist.
They never even ask about you.
Do you know how inhumane they are?
Even when we sent word that Pavitra was no
more, not a single person turned up.
How can you even think about
going back to such people?
Dad, it is human to commit mistakes,
and it's up to humans to set things right.
Let her go, Buddy.
So far… with those people…
Buddy. I take responsibility
for her whole trip.
-What if something goes wrong?
-Behead me.
I won't go, uncle.
He keeps calling and texting me every
minute. What a torture!
Going there feels no different
from staying here.
Listen, dear. I swear on our
friendship and you and say that
None of us would disturb you
during these ten days.
Give your every update to him.
He'll inform me,
and I'll pass it on to him.
-Hey!
-You need not tell anyone.
-Jyothi.
-Reporting, sir.
-Get in touch with the aviation people.
-I'll do it, sir.
-Also, hire the best security in India.
-Done, sir.
-What if there's a mistake?
-Take away my torso.
Should I call Rolex
for the security agency in India?
What for?
So that you and that Rolex
can pocket the commission?
I don't trust people. I only trust Google.
Dear Lord, I don't know
what auspicious moment
made me name my company as
India's Number-One Security Agencies,
every batch of Google-dependent folks
who lose their way ends up at my doorstep.
Happies!
But the sad truth is,
I haven't been able to satisfy
any of those customers.
Forget about customers. You're not able
to satisfy your employees as well.
Hey, agent Ahobhilam…
I brought six lathis for security
purpose the other day.
I could find only four now.
-Where are the remaining two?
-Who knows? We must've lost them.
When the security office itself
has no security for its items…
How would I satisfy you?
Dear Lord, may my company
soar beyond the sky’s limit.
-Excuse me, sir.
-Yes.
Who is Mr. Janardhan Sunnipenta?
-Is it that Murthy who sent you?
-Wow!
Amazing talent!
How did you figure that out, sir?
Only Murthy knows my full name.
Why take that ugly name of
Janardhan Sunnipenta?
Dear Lord, that's all for now.
That's why I named myself Jon Snow.
Agent Jon Snow.
-What's your name?
-I'm Ram, sir.
I can change it to Robinhood
to suit the agency.
You seem like a sharp guy.
What were you doing before this?
I used to wake up late.
Because I was jobless.
If you offer me this job,
I'll wake up early.
Customers would enjoy having
someone humorous like you.
It was you who selected us, sir.
Isn't it?
When you dig a borewell,
you're first greeted with mud water.
Just like you.
Mineral water follows later,
just like him.
Your timing is on a different level, sir.
One minute.
Hello?
Am I speaking to India's number one
security agency from Google?
-Yes. Agent Jon Snow speaking.
-I'm calling from Australia.
We need the best security service.
Can you provide it?
-Hello!
-Hey! A call from Australia.
-They need the best security services.
-Why did they call us then?
Shut up, you good for nothing idiot!
Please continue.
Ms. Neera Vasudev, the daughter of
AV Pharmaceuticals MD is coming to India.
I need your services
from Hyderabad Airport to Rudrakonda
and back to the airport until
ma'am boards her flight.
-Are you okay with it?
-Sure, sir.
And I require Z+ category service.
Hey, how many people are included
in the Z+ category, huh?
Do you think someone working for you
would know anything about such things?
Six.
Any idea how much that would cost for six?
Tell him you're connecting him
with the reservation team.
Reservation team?
-But we don't have one.
-And he's not aware of that.
Good idea!
We're transferring this call
to the reservation team.
Okay.
Wow!
They've got a waiting tone too.
Have you noticed how big the company is?
It's like taking the elevator.
-Thanks for connecting with us.
-I hoped it'd last longer.
Okay, yeah?
If you fill-up the details on our website
and transfer the amount,
we'll assign Z+ category
security for you. Thank you.
How much would it be?
Our expenses cost around ₹ 40,000.
Should I quote ₹ 60,000?
They may bargain for a discount.
Quote ₹ 70,000 to be on the safer side.
-He might go away if we quote that much.
-One lakh.
Aw, snap! That was a precious deal!
You've messed it up.
It's a great deal!
Why would anyone give us ₹ One lakh?
I didn't quote in rupees.
Dollars.
Dollars?!
Dude,I thought he was sharp.
But he turned out to be a scrap.
-But ₹ one lakh sounds cheap.
-Did they say rupees?
It is India's number-one
security agency. It's in dollars.
-Australian dollars?!
-Did they tell you that?
India's number-one security agency,
US Dollars. Transfer the amount.
He just transferred
₹ 75 lakh to our account!
Why is he calling me again?
Will he say he sent it by accident
and demand a refund?
He transferred as soon as we asked.
It means we asked for too little.
Do one thing. Answer the phone
and say we received the advance.
What advance?
He'll ask you the same question.
Tell him to hand us one lakh in advance
and another once the job is over.
He already paid us ₹ 75 lakhs.
-It doesn't look good on us.
-You tell him.
We received the advance.
What advance?
Pay us one lakh in advance
and another after it is done.
-See you on the sixth.
-Yes.
When I prayed to God,
I hoped he would show mercy on me,
but I never expected
he would send you directly.
I'm telling you openly, my boy.
This company never handled
a project worth more than ₹ 25,000 rupees.
I got tensed, receiving a sum of
a crore and a half all of a sudden,
and my BP went down.
Please don't worry.
I'll handle everything.
You're paying me ₹ 50 lakh.
Can't I do that much?
₹ 50 lakhs? What?!
Alright. ₹ 50 lakhs is fixed.
Sir, do we have a security team with us?
Are you asking if there's security?
Boys!
Sir, they're asking for the Z+ category!
-These people look like 70 odd and 80 odd.
-What?
-Can't we manage with them?
-We need people to manage them first.
We need to change our
setup and appearance.
How?
All clear.
My boy.
Do you think everything is correct?
Everything is fine, but
we should have avoided the banner, sir.
Calm down, my boy.
We're handling an international project
for the first time.
How can we not do
even that little publicity?
But the publicity shouldn't be
that low-grade, sir.
It has to be…
very classy…
-Sir…
-Hmm?
Usually, girls use filters
in photos to look good.
My goodness, this girl is
so beautiful, for real!
You are excited looking at that girl.
I'm worried about the guy
coming from behind.
What's wrong with that guy?
He's looking like a
police dog in formal wear!
-What if he finds us out?
-Don't get tensed.
If he asks you
any controversial questions,
say it is confidential.
I'll take care of the rest.
That's it, huh?
You becoming a millionaire
is assured, sir.
Welcome to Hyderabad, ma'am.
This is agent Robinhood.
I'm reporting from India's
number-one security agency.
How was your flight, ma'am?
It was bad.
Can you do something about it?
Let me take it for you.
Yeah.
Welcome, Miss Neera, who returned
from a foreign nation to her homeland.
This is agent Jon Snow.
-How are you?
-I'm doing good. How about you?
-I'm very good, ma'am.
-I don't think so. It's below average.
Thank you.
Would a ₹ 100 bouquet
get our boss on your side?
You'll get smacked!
Sir, this girl is acting a bit odd.
The less we speak, the better.
Why bother, my boy?
They're paying us ₹ 1.5 crore.
Forget about their repartee!
I don't even mind if they spit on my face.
You're forgetting that
you're a human being.
Money plus she.
That's all that matters to us
at the moment.
Let's go.
Ma'am, you're too bossy.
You just rattled their confidence!
-Jyothi.
-Yeah, ma'am.
Like the silent letter "T"
in the word "tsunami,"
you should remain silent
in front of me.
What the hell is this?
Hey! You promised us
Z+ category security…
but only brought
these six guys!
Confidential.
What do you mean by confidential?
Hello--
Sir…Sir…Sir…
There are only six people
around Mr. Modi.
Does that mean his security team
consists of only six people?
What then?
Look over there. Do you see that guy
waving from a distance?
-Who do you think he is?
-Who?
He's one of us, sir.
-Is it so?
-He's on duty facing that way.
Look over there—he,
who is leaving with the bag.
-Is he too one of us?
-Are you still doubting?
Oh my!
Why is he sincerely getting on the flight?
He might accidentally go to
the wrong place!
-Hey, stop him!
-If he goes,
he'll return on the evening flight, sir.
Now that's dedication!
You should be aware that
you can see more than just us.
Many people you don't know
surround you.
-You're being closely monitored.
-Wow!
Ma'am…
Ma'am.
If you need anything in Hyderabad,
please let me know.
-Is it?
-Yes, ma'am.
Do you see those white lines
in the middle of the road?
-Yes, ma'am.
-How many are there?
Confidential.
Ah! It's too hot.
Ma'am, here's your itinerary.
You'll stay at the hotel today.
We're leaving for Rudrakonda
tomorrow morning.
Tomorrow morning's plan is
good enough. But we're going out today.
Jon Snow knows the entire Hyderabad.
Right?
Take me to a great place.
Sure, ma'am.
Give me the bag.
I can handle it.
Thank you.
These rich people
don't trust people like us.
They are suspicious of what we might
snatch from the bag.
Why should we bother, my boy?
We are getting one and a half crores
in one week. Our future looks bright.
You've become calculative.
Tell me the truth. Is the guy making
dosas on that cart one of your people?
You're wrong, sir. The guy making tea
next to that is one of ours.
Ah snap!
I couldn't figure it out at all.
It's no wonder that you are
India's number-one security agency.
What a team!
What a secur--
I heard it is hard
to get an Australian visa.
-That's right.
-Then how did they give it to you?
What did he ask?
Confidential.
Starting tomorrow,
the All India Handicraft Summit
will take place in Hyderabad for a week.
The Chief Minister and
the Home Minister
will attend on the last day.
-You better take care of the security.
-But sir…
I'm on the Robinhood case.
Yeah, right!
He said so much about you,
like an AV at the audio function.
Despite calling yourself Victor,
it doesn't look like this case
will have victory.
What did you say?
A wild dog? Huh?
Just a street dog.
Dogs are best suited for guarding.
Go and take care of security.
I will make sure who gets this case.
Apologies, sir, I will be on sick leave
for a week starting tomorrow.
You seem okay to me. What's wrong?
I got injured from a misfire
while cleaning the gun.
Once I recover from it,
I will catch Robinhood, sir.
Thank you.
Why did you bring me here?
Ma'am… what did you ask us?
I asked you to take me
to the best place.
-Jyothi.
-Yes, ma'am.
Do whatever it takes to get his name
on next year’s Padma Shri awardees list.
Blessed kid!
Thank you very much, ma'am.
WhatsApp me your Aadhar card copy.
You are taking just about anything from
them because of money.
Why should we bother, my boy?
We are getting one and a half crores
in one week. Our future looks bright.
Just stop it!
-Mr. Jyothi?
-Yes, sir.
-Are you crying?
-There's no recognition, Mr. Snow.
While it was I who
found out a gem like you,
won't it hurt when she recommends
Padma Shri to you instead of me?
I'm not jealous of you.
I just feel sad that I'm not getting it.
No, Jyothi.
No.
Mother. They took away my chocolates.
Tomorrow is my birthday.
Please buy them for me.
I don't have enough cash, Pinky.
Let's come back tomorrow and
purchase them.
-₹ 9,500, ma'am.
-Actually…
I don't need this much.
I'll come back next week and buy this.
Congratulations, ma'am!
You're our 10,000th customer.
So, everything you purchase
today is on the house!
-Can I get all these?
-Yes, ma'am.
And my chocolates?
These chocolates are all yours.
Wow!
Thanks, uncle.
Mother, I'll give these chocolates
to all my friends. I'm so happy.
Jon Snow.
Jon! Jon!
Agent Jon Snow is here.
Run for your lives, guys!
-Jon?
-Snow?
Knock me dead.
Wow!
Jon Snow!
Peace.
I don't like it.
Sir, you are in a
different league altogether!
This is unexpected.
I wanted to raise the expectations.
So, I arranged those six guys.
Do you mean you set those guys up?
They're paying us ₹ 1.5 crore!
Shouldn't they feel satisfied with us?
That's why I planned this.
They will start seeing us
in a different perspective.
He simply became my fan.
Sir, just one photo, please.
Okay.
To be very frank,
you're pretty cunning, sir.
A man must be cunning.
I’d only heard of superheroes
but saw one for the first time
in the supermarket. Thank you!
-Jyothi.
-Ma'am.
-We start at nine tomorrow.
-Got it, ma'am.
Good night.
Your sincerity is
genuinely humbling, bro.
-Do you stay here day and night?
-It's my duty, sir. It's unavoidable.
Hats off! You're the best.
Now that I'm here,
please give me some tea.
-Thank you.
-Hey, give me tea.
-Hey!
-Just give him.
It's bad, just as expected.
-Ugh!
-But it's okay.
You call this tea?
No taste, nothing!
Why are you shouting?
Does he look like
a professional tea seller?
-India's number one--
-Sir!
-No, sir.
-Shh!
I'm not going to tell you.
Even if I lose my life, I won't tell you.
What now?
Didn't you like the tea? Get lost!
Hey! What are you talking about?
Hey! If I decide, your shop
won't even exist tomorrow.
Hey! What will you do, huh?
Once we leave in the morning,
he won’t keep his shop open.
You won't even find
any evidence. Get lost!
Get the hell out!
-Go away!
-I'm going.
Sir!
-Okay, okay. No problem.
-Sir!
You didn't pay for the tea, sir.
What are you, man?
If you're still acting like
a tea seller even after all this,
-What acting?
-I'd have married you if you were a girl.
Promise!
-Only if you're a girl.
-Something's wrong with him.
A person's body has many parts
like the head, neck, and heart.
If you move, even I don't know
which part I'll slice open.
Who the hell are you guys?
-We're here for the Australian girl.
-What do you have to do with her?
To understand that, you first
need to know about our village.
We're from Rudrakonda.
It's the Nagulapalli forest area.
Greenery and fresh water
are our wealth.
We used to chop those trees
for our livelihood.
As we destroyed
the life-giving forest,
a great man entered our lives.
He had us plant saplings with the same
hands that once chopped down trees.
He taught us farming,
and the value of helping fellow humans.
He's our guiding light, Mr. Vishwanath.
Before we could celebrate
the arrival of Ramarajya in Rudrakonda,
almost like Ravana coming from Lanka,
the ominous footsteps of a demon
were heard in our village.
This village is mine from this moment.
With the Lord as my witness!
I could harvest a small piece of land.
But how can I manage the entire village?
The villagers and Mr. Vishwanath would
never permit cannabis cultivation here.
Go and convince them.
Is Shekaram home?
-Can you call--
-What do you want?
-I'm here for Shekaram. Please call him.
-I'm Shekaram.
You are Shekaram?
Where's Shekaram?
Don't you understand?
That's my wife.
And that's my daughter.
I'm Shekaram!
Subbulu uncle.
Subbulu uncle
sold me the house
and left for somewhere.
And you are?
Why don't you believe I'm Raju?
Give me a soda, Shankaranna.
The whole village was
under his control.
He's severed all ties between
our village and the outside world.
No message, no word,
and no sign of anyone.
He's turned us into mute spectators.
He made our elderly man,
who supported us, disabled.
He doesn't know how to convince.
He only knows how to eliminate.
We don't know why, but he now
wants the leader's granddaughter.
We must save the girl, somehow.
There's no time. His men
will be here soon. Where is she?
Kali!
They are taking away the girl.
It's over. It's all over.
They're taking the girl away.
Do something.
Mr. Snow.
What's this nuisance?
We allotted rooms for you to rest.
Why are you making a ruckus here?
Please don't disturb me.
It's like watching a
Spanish movie without subtitles!
What on earth is going on here?
I'm confused about the same thing, sir.
Selfish fellow!
All the Indians are the same.
Not you, I was referring
to the village guy.
He'd been demanding minute-by-minute
updates from me since we started.
I gave him a second-by-second update.
Now, when I want an update
he's not even answering my call.
-Selfish fellow!
-What updates?
Sir, did you land at the airport?
No, I'm at the bus stand.
Come here with an auto.
Which hotel are you staying in, sir?
-Movotel, man. Will you pay the bill?
-Please don't get mad, sir.
Non-sense!
Hang up the phone!
-Sir, what is ma'am's room number?
-Why would you need that?
If you tell us the number,
our Pandit will share the room's Feng Shui
and the occupants' horoscopes.
Kissik!
-Is it true?
-It's true, sir.
It's 2013.
Tell me her horoscope,
and I'll impress her.
Are you still there?
She is my girl--
Hello?
He asked for many details, but
didn't he ask for her photo?
That's right, Mr. Robin.
He didn't ask,
and I didn't even think about sending it.
I won't send it anyway.
I'm not talking to that selfish fellow!
Okay, Mr. Robin.
Okay, Mr. Hood, I mean Mr. Snow.
Why are you shivering, sir?
Do you want me to turn off the AC?
Would anyone sweat under the AC?
Since the moment I heard about that Swami,
even my clothes are sweating from fear.
If need be, I'll even work as security
at a teenage girl's party,
but I'll never step
into that village!
He might ruin everything.
Sir, haven't you figured it out yet?
What should I figure?
Unaware that you set up
six guys there, I set up ten guys here.
Was it you who set them?
They're paying us ₹ 1.5 crore.
Shouldn't they feel satisfied about it?
I got worried,
thinking they were for real.
Goodnight, then. We need
to wake up early. There's a lot to do.
Sir. You haven't given me a selfie.
You'll have it soon. But…
What's with the mountain image
on your shirt?
Since we're going to Rudrakonda,
I thought it would be symbolic.
On the way, there's a village
called Langalapalli.
Would you like to wear
a Langa to be symbolic?
Langa?
Oh my god! You're ferociously
and equally hilarious, sir.
Whatever you say or do is wonderful!
I'm expecting two selfies from you.
I won't accept no for an answer.
My boy.
Wow! How she opens the door!
Anyone would open a car's door
the same way.
She closed it just as beautifully.
If a girl like her enters my life,
wherever she goes, my network follows.
Gucci Baby
Don’t stab me with those looks!
Little heart
Don’t break it with your hooks!
"Love you, Rasna!"
I said and chased you around
90s kid, that’s who I am now!
First look
knocked out like All Out!
You're Boost's energy, no doubt!
Kiss me like an Amul baby
Your taste? The best!
Gold medal? You deserve it!
Won’t switch sides, you can trust it!
Your touch, smooth like silk
Lux soap would approve of it!
Wherever you go, I follow
Wherever you go, I follow, bae!
Fresh and juicy babe
You’re my Frooti beauty, no debate!
Born tough babe
Like a CEAT tyre!
"Taste the thunder," babe!
I'm your Thums Up, through and through!
Life’s full of sweetness
Like Dairy Milk, when you're around!
Our pair? So strong!
Sticks forever like the Fevicol bond!
Age? Santoor glow stays on!
Craze? Your town knows it all!
Your love? A masterpiece!
One Perk and you lighten up
But my heart weight just stacks up!
"I love you" leaves you speechless
Time to switch on your brain, princess!
Wherever you go, I follow
Wherever you go, I follow, bae!
Wow!
Beautiful!
Rudrakonda.
Ma'am!
Why did you come here, ma'am?
Please leave immediately.
You can't be here.
Leave immediately, ma'am!
All those who dared
to warn the girl not to come here
were hanged right in front of your eyes.
Yet, you ask her to leave?
Don't you have any fear?
Please answer me, foreign girl.
After Swami went through all the trouble
to track down your number,
threatened your aunt
and her kids with a knife
to make them call you
and drag you here…
who are these guys
to say you shouldn't come?
They also sent men to warn you.
They made a mistake and were punished.
It's good that I came.
Otherwise…
along with these men
the rest of the villagers
would also have lost their lives.
That means all these guys
are the real deal, huh?
Oh my gosh!
-No! No! No!
-Stop!
Sir, why are you shaking with anger?
Please calm down.
When warriors like you fight,
soldiers like us end up dying.
Please calm down. I beg you.
Please don't.
This guy doesn't know
the difference between
trembling in fear and shaking with rage.
Who are you all?
Swami went to another village for a deal.
You'll know everything once he's back.
Until then,
save yourself, these people,
and your grandfather.
Grandfather.
Hey, security!
I heard one of you switched the
room number and deceived my guy.
How could he be so foolish?
As long as you’re here,
our guy will be the security
for you and your foreign girl.
-Hey, Gana!
-With the Lord as my witness!
It's not you he needs, dear.
He’s after the license your dad owns.
The Indian Medical Council’s license
allowing your company to set up
a pharmaceutical unit in India.
With that license,
one can legally cultivate cannabis here.
His plan is
to run his business undisturbed
under the guise of medical transport.
That's why he made you come here.
If that happens, it will destroy
not only our village but several others
and many lives will be lost.
To avoid that,
-you need to leave this place.
-What are you saying, Grandpa?
What's the system
and the police doing about all this?
Their lack of action
tells you how powerful he is,
doesn't it, dear?
Before he sets foot here,
you need to get out of this place.
How can I leave you like this?
I sent your mother away that day so
you wouldn't face these circumstances.
And today, I'm asking you
to leave for the same reason.
He's a monster, dear!
Please, son, get the girl out of
here by any means necessary.
Boss! They're escaping.
Begin the hunt.
-Hey, that way!
-Oh, no!
Sir, it would have been better if you
were in that car for security reasons.
Exactly!
Finally!
You applied the brakes.
Is it break time now?
What the hell?
Why did he bring us here?
And he's honking.
Shit!
Tango to Charlie.
Turn the car around immediately.
Alright, over.
Can you hear me?
Respond if you do. Over.
Hey, this is too much. Over.
Does this walkie work at all?
Cotton?
Cotton!
Mr. Snow. Mr. Snow!
What the hell is this?
Cotton.
Is it for cushioning?
Garbage, my son!
They've given us
a contract of ₹ 1.5 crore.
Couldn't you at least
bring original walkies?
So, are these dummy walkies?
They held knives to your people
to bring you here.
If you leave now,
you’ll have no one left
in the village to call your own.
So, those rowdies in the supermarket?
-Each one charged 25,000 rupees.
-With GST.
What a deception!
People like you don't deserve to live!
I've become a fool because of you!
You aren't the fool here.
When a ₹ 100 walkie-talkie is a dummy,
look at me thinking this gun was real.
I'm the big fool here.
A world-famous fool!
All the hens escaped
and reached the poultry farm.
With the Lord as our witness,
we must give them a taste of death.
You have the mindset to help strangers.
So how could you leave your family
and village in this situation?
-How?
-I don't want to leave, Robin.
-But I don't even know what to--
-Why should you do anything, ma'am?
You're paying us ₹ 1.5 crore.
It's our job to give you
the satisfaction of money well spent.
India is my country.
All Indians are my brothers and sisters.
How dare you enter my country
and disturb my family members?
You bloody outsiders!
Shit, shit!
Ma'am!
Ma'am! No!
A king’s actual strength
isn’t in his sword or crown.
It is in the army
that stands before him!
Boys!
This is your army.
And that is our strength.
Should we flee in fear of him?
Or shall we fight for your people?
The final decision is yours, ma'am.
They say if the cause is noble,
you don't need weapons.
With someone like you by my side,
we can face anyone.
Even greater than
the ₹ 1.5 crore they offer,
I’m experiencing the real thrill now.
It's not ₹ 1.5 crore, sir.
It's 6.5!
₹ 6.5 crore?
No matter where Robinhood
is hiding in the world,
I'll drag him out.
The sword hanging around
his neck is named Victor.
He follows no particular cause or agenda.
All he cares about is money.
He'll oppose anyone to get it.
That, Varada, is my character.
I can easily break your bones
and take the girl away.
You must've already
understood that by now.
Quote a number that shows
you could stop me, too.
And we'll close the deal.
₹ One crore.
With the Lord as my witness!
Five crore rupees.
Ma'am, we'll escape first and then fight.
We can outsource it.
Or I'll drop you off safely
and personally return to fight.
It's a scam. Don't fall for it. Okay?
-That's it.
-Let's fight!
Trace enormous donations
to any orphanage immediately.
If he's Robinhood, then I'm Victor here.
I’ll show him what Victor’s
master plan looks like.
Agent Robinhood and team
reporting, ma'am. On duty 24/7.
Swami, your stuff is gold.
But before you go
for an international drug deal,
you should know about Alex.
He's a master drug tester.
Once he tests and approves it,
David bhai will hand you
a one-year international contract.
That's why all the high-range groups
are anticipating this deal.
But Shukla can't stand it
when a new player enters the deal.
What did you say?
That your stuff is more potent than mine?
Deena worked for me all these days.
And now, you're using him
to replace me in David Bhai's team
and enter the international
drug market, huh?
What is this stuff?
This stuff is out of this world!
Whose weed is this?
Swami's weed.
Hey, Siri. Call David.
I just tried the new guy's stuff.
It's freaking amazing!
-How much is he quoting?
-He--
Money isn't important.
We just want to enter the market.
Can you bring tons of stuff here
without getting caught by the police?
Take the advance if you can.
Swami,
he's asking if you can cross
all check posts and deliver the stuff.
Tell him the police open the
gates to let the stuff through.
Welcome to the club!
From now on, David owns you.
You reached this position
by replacing someone else.
I'm replacing you.
Congratulate me.
Go on.
Please don't mind me saying this, ma'am.
-You staying here is quite dangerous.
-Let's leave.
Finally!
The village is counting on me.
Let’s set it free and then leave.
This village is counting on you?
-Which idiot told you that?
-Nature.
Many great souls fought for freedom.
But we attained freedom only
under Mahatma Gandhi’s leadership.
Even he didn't know whether
we would attain it. But he fought anyway.
Nature took care of the rest.
What is he saying?!
Many have fought for freedom—
Yes, their struggle was justified,
but what’s this guy’s issue?
Confidential.
He's right, Jyothi!
What looks dangerous today
might not be threatening tomorrow.
Today’s truth
can become a lie tomorrow.
Who knows?
What kind of illogical statement is this?
How can today's truth
become a lie tomorrow?
Common sense--
That's basic, ma'am.
Good question.
-What's today?
-Monday.
That's the truth.
What if I come tomorrow
and call it a Monday?
-Tell me, Jyothi.
-A lie.
That's what I said. Right?
Amazing!
Madame Curie, Mother Teresa and Monalisa.
If we blend all their qualities,
it's you, ma'am!
Oh my god! I'm surprised.
I'm feeling inferior
looking at you, ma'am.
Not just you, Robin…
even my Dad feels the same way.
I have had a high IQ since childhood.
What's IQ, ma'am?
Who named our hand as "the hand"?
It wasn't me, sir.
Who first called our head "the head"?
-Uhh…
-I know it wasn't you.
Similarly, someone used the term
IQ for IQ for the first time.
Why should we bother about such details?
Alright. What's our next move?
How can we hold a torch to the Sun?
Can we ideate better than you?
Ma'am, your target is now our target.
You handle Swami and Co.'s exit strategy,
and we'll execute it.
We must know the enemy's strength
and network before engaging in battle.
To find that out,
we must stay in this village.
Yes, ma'am.
If we go to Grandpa's house,
he'll be worried that we're still here.
So…
until the situation is under control,
we'll have to stay somewhere around here.
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm full of doubts.
-Please tell me what's going on.
-What's your doubt, sir? Ask me.
Alright, she asked you.
But how did you set this place up?
I brought you all here because I knew
this place was under Varada's control.
You're so cunning, my boy.
Didn't you tell me that
human nature is cunning?
What's that you're spraying, sir?
Body spray?
Does anyone spray
body spray into their mouth?
-Anxiety spray.
-Oh.
First, you said ₹ 1.5 crore,
and then, you said 6.5 crores.
You also talk about the village's freedom.
What's your actual plan?
₹ 6000 crores!
₹ 6000 crores?!
-Where are they?
-What do you mean by where they are?
They are walking around so sweetly
with expensive shoes…
right before my eyes.
Billionaire.
It's wrong to trap a girl for money.
It's wrong to like a girl for her money,
but it's not wrong
if the girl you like has money.
Anyway, I'm doing all this
to boost your range and mine.
How?
If the girl falls for me,
you'll automatically get
her company's security contract.
India's number-one agency
will become the world's number-one.
Wow!
The thought is so wonderful.
By the way,
can you impress that girl?
Robin!
I love this place, man!
Not the place, dear.
You're the kind of person I could have
as my security for life.
You've impressed me.
One look is enough, my love
I already feel so lucky
Will you give me an igniting touch?
One more time… One more time…
I may look like a thug
But a hug will melt me down
No delays, just give it to me now!
One more time… One more time…
Never before have I felt this way
Even when close by
No anger, so strange!
They said I don't fall for anyone
But it all changes today
Why doesn't this guy stay in one place?
Taan tarikita din din na na
Let go of that shyness, come closer
One more time… One more time…
Taan tarikita din din na na
Break the limits, cross the line
Tarikita tarikita ta
One look is enough, my love
I already feel so lucky
Will you give me an igniting touch?
One more time… One more time…
I may look like a thug
But a hug will melt me down
No delays, just give it to me now!
One more time… One more time… Yeah!
Oh my love
My lovely rage
Your body is a beauty package
Oh my love, one look at you
And my heart is frozen still
Because of you
Even my sleep is damaged
In the day
You're the star on Earth
At night, I'm your shadow
Always by your side
To my dream castle
You're the queen
And I become a king
Just without a crown
My pride never fades
My name stands tall
But one glance at you, and I fall
Never before have I felt this way
Won’t you just stay still
For a moment?
Taan tarikita din din na na
Let go of that shyness, come closer
One more time… One more time…
Taan tarikita din din na na
Break the limits, cross the line
Tarikita tarikita ta
That fraud!
Hail the Lord!
To escape from a great danger,
you all must make a promise.
What's that, boss?
If Swami knows that
someone came and hit us,
our death is inevitable.
We must all stand by the same word.
The foreign girl came.
After warning her,
we placed her on the hilltop.
Nothing more happened here.
It should be as if nothing had happened.
With the Lord as our witness!
How does he know your number?
-No clue, boss.
-That fraud!
Block him!
[in unison] Block him, boss.
Swami has come, boss.
Was the deal successful, Swami?
Swami…
The foreign girl is here.
I placed her on the hilltop house
after a warning.
I'll figure out what
to do next from Premji.
We're about to step into
the international market.
Yet there's no sign of excitement or joy.
What's going on, Premji?
Swami,
you know your horoscope mirrors
that of Ravana, whom we worship.
Ravana, a man of great wisdom and power,
was destroyed because
he went after a woman.
So you've made sure
there's no place for a woman
in your life or in the lives
of those around you.
This deal isn't right for us, Swami.
Send that girl away.
Or else, your downfall--
I did this to stop those words
in your throat, Premji.
The entire world must know
about the greatness of our stuff!
For my growth…
This is a war that I’m waging!
Something's in the farm, Swami.
With the Lord as my witness!
Pathetic.
Reading the reviews about your company
makes me want to cry and spit
for trusting someone like you.
Sir.
I cannot tolerate you
ridiculing my company, sir.
It's not just me, you dimwit.
It's resounding across Google.
This guy's review says that he hired
you as security for a wedding feast,
but some outsiders
still snuck in and had dinner.
He's given you a half-star rating.
-Hey, Ahobhilam.
-Sir.
-Who gave us that half-star rating?
-It's Daniel, sir.
The contract was for 4,500 rupees,
but he deducted 500.
That's it, sir.
He deducted 500 rupees.
So I brought my family to have biryani.
He took them to be outsiders
and gave us a half-star rating.
Please don't trust Google, sir.
I don't trust people.
I only trust Google.
You clown!
I don't feel sad because I
handed you a ₹ 1.5 crore contract. No.
Remember I asked for a selfie
with you in excitement?
I can't share this with anyone,
nor can I stay silent.
I just have to walk away.
I must walk away.
Robin.
Rob--
Didn't you already have breakfast?
-Yes.
-What's this, then?
I wanted to give her the satisfaction
that I had stopped eating
and rushed to her when she called.
-What about my satisfaction?
-Then eat.
You are more dangerous than
that Ganja batch.
They seem like kids compared to you.
-Ma'am.
-You could've finished eating, Robin.
Listening to you is more
important to me than eating, ma'am.
Let's go out.
-Ma'am. Uniform…
-You look good.
Where are we headed, ma'am?
Rural Community Development
Why are we here, ma'am?
Do you know why I asked you
not to wear the uniform today?
You are still thinking in a controlled
way, like one of my subordinates.
You should think at the
same level as I do
to complete a mission like ours.
You should grasp my ideas
while I'm still thinking about them.
-Actually--
-I got it, ma'am.
You wrote three points on the board.
The first point is to
know everything related to the enemy.
We came here to find out about
the villagers and the officer.
Am I right?
That's my boy!
A candle gives light, but it needs
a fire like you to ignite, ma'am!
Is everyone healthy?
Yes.
Are they receiving
the tribal subsidies on time?
Yes.
Are there any issues?
No.
Tell me if there are any issues.
Government appointed me
to take care of you.
Rumor has it that cannabis is
being secretly grown in the agency.
If that's true, just lodge a complaint.
-I'll take action.
-You should take action, Collector.
Why is ma'am here?
Who are you? Who should we
take action against?
I'm Viswanath's granddaughter.
One person has been causing trouble
to these villagers for many years.
-Why are you still here?
-His name is--
No. Don't say anything.
Your grandfather is worried about you.
-Please leave this place, ma'am.
-Just go!
Leave, ma'am!
Tell Grandpa I'll be back in the evening.
-It's not that.
-Go!
-Please listen to me--
-Stop!
If you feel like saying anything,
here's my number.
Call me anytime.
Do you think committing murders
is part of the Olympics?
You’re on a killing spree,
like you’re competing for a gold medal.
Why did you kill that Goa dealer?
Now, we’ll have no clue who’s
backing him or what they’re planning.
Upon learning that AV Pharma made
a cannabis-based cancer drug,
I moved their file within the government
deeming that company essential to us.
Knowing Abhinav Vasudev
wouldn’t yield to money,
I gave you his family details
and made sure his daughter came here.
I got you an entry to international
drug dealing through Deena.
As expected, you got David's contract.
Just like entering the international
market is important to you,
coming back to power next time
is equally important to me.
Until this happens, just focus
on the goods and the license.
-Did you speak to the girl?
-She's on her way here.
Why hold back after coming this far?
Step out.
-What?
-The second point you wrote on the board.
-Meet your enemy.
-Oh, right!
Yes.
-Bro…
-Yeah?
Oh my God!
What a huge crop!
Collector Sir.
You said you'll take action
against people cultivating cannabis.
Please take action, sir.
Ma'am.
Sir’s action there was intentional.
You are right, Robin!
I got it, ma'am.
I didn't get it.
Isn't this your next step?
Oh!
That's my boy!
Blank cheque!
Write as many crores as you want.
Leave this village, and if you can,
this country too.
Premji told me never to harm a woman.
That's the only reason
the axe missed you.
Money isn't important for Swami.
The market is important.
We will begin the harvest once we get
a message from the international market.
Before that,
we should possess a license
that belongs to a local.
If you expose this issue
or blow it out of proportion,
the entire town will
turn into a graveyard.
Go.
He asked for your license. Right?
I’ll tell him on your behalf
that you won't let this deal happen.
With the Lord as my witness!
He's just a showoff, sir!
It's just buildup!
In fact, he stopped
even before you raised your arm.
With the Lord as my witness!
For the first time, I'm seeing someone
who thinks money isn’t important.
For me, money is everything.
Varada promised me ₹ 5 crores
to keep the girl in the village.
He's not responding
to my calls and messages now.
He blocked me on WhatsApp this morning.
Looks like the beating I gave
that fool wasn't enough.
Hey! What do you mean, beating me?
Do you have the guts
to take on Swami's guys?
Hey! Looks like you don't know.
Swami has already seen
the complete film on a 70 mm screen.
Even the collector had no idea
that we arrived by car.
Then, how did he know?
He's not a magician.
But… he's a good technician.
[In Tamil] Didn't you understand?
Do you think that's a scarecrow?
It has a camera.
There's also a camera in this tree.
There are a total of eight cameras here.
The list includes the one
in the seat the minister occupies.
Did you know that, Mr. Minister?
He's placed cameras in the entire village
and turned the entire village
into a big boss house
by watching the visuals on his phone.
With the Lord as my witness!
I don't know why such things
are visible only to me.
I'm worried about what else I'll notice
and reveal in the coming days.
Coronavirus gets you
14 days of quarantine.
If it's me, it'll be lifelong!
Please don't keep me here for too long.
You discovered something
no one else could find all these days.
You must be felicitated.
Come!
I don't give free hugs.
I'll hug you if you pay me my money.
Hey, Swami. Don't.
-Collector, I'm taking the vehicle.
-Don't do anything rash. Listen!
If we kill him now,
the news will reach Australia.
Please don't hurt anyone
until we close this deal.
Alright? Please.
We got the official confirmation.
It's time to rejoice!
Fix the time for the harvest.
And I'll plan the party.
Just a little!
-Enough.
-Assistant sir,
are you certain that the girl will return?
We came here only after we
were informed she'd be here.
Jon Snow, what's the status?
On the way, sir.
What? Did you hear it on that walkie?
Let's try the rasam.
The texture is excellent!
Has anyone appreciated
your rasam before?
-No. No one said it.
-Then, why did you make it?
There's neither salt nor taste in it!
My stomach's upset.
Sister, where did you
dump the wastewater?
Did you put it here?
In India, they don't
put salt in wastewater.
We felt a sense of relief
knowing you're coming back, dear.
We can all be happy
once you hand him that license, dear.
Are you okay, ma'am?
-Jyothi, it's not okay.
-What?
Ma'am almost killed Swamy.
It was a close call.
Is it true, ma'am?
Ma'am?
I was irritated listening to his nonsense.
I found an axe nearby and threw it.
-Axe?
-Not the body spray.
A real axe!
Are you serious, ma'am?
I need to freshen up.
Just like dancing to an emotional song,
is there a connection between her
body language and the hype you created?
What exactly is your plan?
Which is the world's oldest animal?
The newest animal is Ranbir Kapoor.
-Oldest is dinosaur?
-No!
-Zebra.
-Zebra?! How?
It's still in black and white!
Known is a drop.
Unknown is an ocean!
Shit, man!
Do you know what you are doing, dear?
I wanted to go back, Grandpa.
I just couldn't leave you like this.
You are stubborn, just like my daughter.
She left with your dad
even when we asked her to stay back.
We thought she'd at least
be happy wherever she was.
But she left this world.
Now, you are staying back
when we are asking you to leave.
What if something bad happens to you?
Every person has a death date
just like a birth date.
But if you are scared of death,
there won't be any value
to the days we live, sir.
Even if you can't physically stand up,
you're still trying to stand up
for this village and your family.
She shares your blood.
How could she leave you
knowing your life is in danger?
If we were scared as children,
we'd ask any of our family
members to stay with us.
That's because being with
a loved one gives us courage.
This fear is contagious, sir.
It had spread so deep in your family.
With just one phone call you made,
the girl came for you.
The girl wanted to
stand by her family in crisis.
Your fear is so intense that
you can't embrace her with love.
Neera…
Ecstasy, ecstasy, ecstasy, ecstasy
Ecstasy, ecstasy it is
Many, many days ago, in Mamidipalli
A farmer got caught at night
While tying the knot
He said he didn't get the subsidy
As he sulked and was asked about it
He showed the crop
It wasn't paddy, it wasn't chili
It wasn't sugarcane
The crop he grew was weed
That is the surprise!
In a posh pub in Jubilee Hills
A super classy guy
Made a flashy entry
He called me Chinni
Then called me Munni
Kept a little distance
Showed a lot of respect
Asked me to come along
And I went to his villa
Said I wasn’t his match
But his daddy had other plans
Turned Munni into his Pinni!
That's the surprise!
A chubby-cheeked boyfriend of mine
Met me in Bangalore one day
So handsome that if he waves his hand
Even second-hand feels brand new
Saw a girl's photo in his wallet
Stopped right there and questioned him
Not his cousin, not his girlfriend
Who is she then?
Well, that was him before surgery!
I wish it had lasted
a little longer. Sigh!
Don't be disappointed.
Neera, shall we continue?
Of course, Robin!
Start the music!
That's the surprise!
If a winning lottery ticket expires
Well, that’s a surprise!
If hidden cash becomes invalid!
If you gift an apple to an Apple phone
Well, that’s a surprise!
If the pot is the best part
Of a pot biryani!
Boom! That’s a crazy surprise!
Many great souls fought for freedom.
But we attained freedom only
under Mahatma Gandhi’s leadership.
-Did you copy my idea?
-I just used it!
Even he didn't know whether
we would attain it. But he fought anyway.
Nature took care of the rest.
We must follow our forefathers' path.
What?
Does this girl have four fathers?
Even though she's a foreign girl,
why is she speaking so openly?
Hey! Tell me the truth.
You failed the 10th standard
English exam, right?
I failed the 7th standard, too. Why?
"Forefathers" doesn't mean she has
four fathers and a troubled mother.
She talked about her ancestors.
Does "ancestors" come under a caste?
Don't get me wrong.
I failed in Telugu too!
-I wish you well, sir.
-Why?
We have only one way ahead.
Please don't support Swami.
No one should go to work.
We are going through
our own share of suffering.
Please don't get involved in this.
You said the village relies on you.
But even that oldie doesn't trust you.
Listen to me.
Let's get out of here quickly, ma'am.
-Please.
-Mr. Jyothi.
Intelligent people always have
more than one plan up their sleeve.
They'll have a plan B.
I got it, ma'am.
If this way isn't possible,
we should attack from the other side.
Am I right?
If not from this side, which side
will you cut your way through?
Jyothi, you always--
-Robin.
-Ma'am?
There's a camera over there.
Where?!
-Don't turn back!
-Okay.
If the ganja gang is so well prepared,
what about intelligent people like us?
I got it, ma'am!
He has cameras.
You want to hack his phone
through the camera access. Right?
That's my boy!
Do it!
Is she really that intelligent?
Do you know who first coined
the term "intelligent people"?
I get it.
It's intelligent people themselves!
That's my boy!
-Jyothi!
-You-- Coming, ma'am.
You're talking without thinking!
What about the phone?
What do you mean by us hacking?
We've already hacked it!
When?!
Yes! We’ve taken control
of Swami’s phone. What next?
Send the same message
to all the contacts.
Okay. Sending!
Your phone has been hacked!
We clicked on a message from your number.
And all our phones got hacked.
Who's trying to stop me?
Who is it?
This Sagar guy is killing me
with his calls!
I can't switch off my phone
or block him.
I should hire a
contract killer to kill him.
Kissik!
Hello?
Are you mad?
-Hang up immediately, ma'am.
-One second.
It's not Swami who's stopping you.
It's that guy. Confirmed.
Jyothi, how can anyone stop me?
-I've decided to give freedom to--
-Stop it, ma'am.
You can't even reply to a message.
Can you free an entire village?
Jyothi!
His intentions are pretty crooked, ma'am.
He's staring at you
while you speak on the phone.
Did he?
With your permission,
I'll expose his intentions today.
Robin!
-Yes, ma'am.
-I'm bored.
I've planned a game.
Whoever the bottle points to
must ask a question to the spinner.
But… Hello!
Why the sports dress?
You said we'll play a game
so I got dressed up.
We're playing truth or dare.
Do we use gloves
or helmets while playing?
Hey, you wastrel!
Keep this there!
-Truth or dare?
-Dare.
He's cheating, ma'am.
I dare you to tell me the truth.
-Truth.
-You didn't receive any call, did you?
-I didn't receive any call.
-That's it!
See, ma'am. His intentions since--
Do you have any girlfriends?
Why bother about his girlfriends?
Irrelevant question. Stick to the mission.
We need more information
to learn about his intentions.
Go for it.
Do you have any girlfriends?
-No, ma'am.
-Why not?
I pledged in my childhood that
"India is my country
and all Indians are
my brothers and sisters."
I'm waiting for a foreign girl
to enter my life.
See ma'am. He's targeting you since--
Why is she feeling shy?
She'll feel shy initially
and then fall for him eventually.
Truth or dare?
Truth.
Ms. Neera, you didn't receive
any call a while ago, right?
Am I supposed to tell
only the truth, Jyothi?
Yes, you should tell the truth, ma'am!
I didn't receive any call.
Ma'am!
If you didn't receive any call,
why were you cat walking in front of him?
What are your intentions?
Tell me.
This isn't your turn, Jyothi.
I'm disqualifying this question.
Mr. Snow…
Mr. Jyothi, what's a place
you visit regularly?
This question is illogical
for the situation.
The world is very illogical, Mr. Jyothi!
How?
-England starts with an "E,"
-Yes.
but India starts with an "I!"
Wow! Impressive Robin!
Thank you!
This question is better
than the situation.
Mr. Jyothi, what's a place
you visit regularly?
Depression! I'm going into depression
every day because of you.
-Karma! Just for a game--
-Is "depression" a place?
I mean… A few
of my clients have been there.
I salute you, messenger!
He's printing and sending all the
information from your phone one by one.
Swami.
Message from David bhai.
He's asking when we'll send him the stuff.
Tell him we'll send it by the 20th.
What if that message
was not sent by David bhai…
but by the hacker?
Isn't it a risk to reveal
the transport date of our stuff?
Don't do it then.
Don't reply to that message.
If that message
was really sent by David bhai…
we'll lose our lives
for not replying to it.
-Ugh!
-What the…
Whoever that guy is,
he's just toying with us.
Does the guy who hacked our phones
know we know they've been hacked?
He may not know it.
Maybe he doesn't know.
-Hey, Deena.
-Swami.
Transfer ₹ 1 crore to the
minister's account for the party.
Alright.
-Tell me.
-There's a good news for you.
All the orphanages received
their monthly money transfers.
But how?
The party received a fund.
I used it up as our fund.
We're busted, buddy!
Check where the amount went.
The amount was transferred to an
account named Ram Dootha Hanuman.
Give me the account details right away.
It's definitely a fake account.
Find out where the amount
went from that account.
The amount was transferred
to orphanages and old age homes, sir.
Don't spare a single orphanage.
Hey!
Since you sent the amount
to orphanages,
I understand how important
they are to you.
I don't know who you are.
All those lives against yours.
It's time to unmask!
Hey, send him my photo.
But buddy…
He should target me,
not the orphanages.
Send him my photo.
With the Lord as my witness!
Ma'am, ma'am.
Swami's men!
Swami's men are here.
-Father-in-law--
-Where's Grandpa?
Grandpa?
-Grandpa?
-Grandpa!
Neera, father-in-law is missing.
Dad is missing!
He isn't upstairs.
Robin. Robin!
Robin's also missing?
That means Grandpa is safe.
After beating him to death, what are
you watching instead of killing him?
We didn't beat him.
We can't beat you in normal conditions.
That's why we sedated you.
All these days, we thought
that the foreign girl was your weakness.
I understood only when Swami told me.
Varada…
That security is here not for the girl…
but for that oldie.
Hey Varada,
they say a guy high on weed
sticks to the same mood he's in.
Right now, I'm only in one mood.
If you lay a finger
on the old man, I'll kill you.
on the old man, I'll kill you!
I'll kill you.
I'm bleeding when hit…
but I can't feel the pain.
Boss!
Usually, a person is sedated
to help him cope with the pain.
But we sedated him in advance.
Now he won't feel any pain, boss.
What am I now?
Like Spiderman and Superman,
am I Manja-man?
Robin!
Escape from here!
They are monsters.
Robin!
My granddaughter is alone there.
They'll harm her.
Let him have his plans.
I have my backup.
I'm the only one here.
But over there…
there are four more like me.
Your granddaughter…
is safe.
What the…?
I see Robin in all four of you.
Who are you guys?
The Nizamuddin Express
to Delhi is running two hours late.
We regret the inconvenience
caused to passengers--
Two hours?
-A little help.
-Hey, get lost.
Chandrayya, do you have any change on you?
Sir, here's your purse.
Thank you.
God bless you, son.
Hey, Robinhood.
Yes, you. Come here.
My name isn't Robinhood.
-It's Ram.
-Your family has chosen a good name.
-Where are they?
-I don't have anyone.
India is my country.
Never say you don't have anyone.
This country is your family.
All the citizens are like family members.
From now on,
call me grandfather.
-Alright?
-Okay.
-Yes?
-We're on our way to Delhi on a task.
We don't know anyone here.
If it isn't too much trouble,
please provide shelter
to the boy for two days.
-I'll take him as soon as I return.
-The boy will be here until you return.
-Kabaddi, kabaddi, kabaddi…
-Ram! Ram!
Grandfather!
-Shall we leave?
-Hey, Ram!
-Come back fast.
-We'll win only with you.
Didn't you say these are all
my family members, Grandpa?
They need me now.
I'll be with you when you need me.
Take it.
But, sir. This is…
You're a constant support
for all these children.
We'll be the support you need.
Henceforth, the responsibility of this guy
and the ashram lies with me.
You'll receive help from us
every month without fail.
You…
Your name?
If I take credit,
the help becomes mine alone.
If I stay anonymous,
it becomes that of humanity.
This is the next generation.
They need to see
people as inherently good.
Ram!
My boy!
I don't know who you are.
But please help me.
A monster is dragging
our elder's granddaughter
from Australia to our village.
The hands that helped us
need our help now.
We risked our lives
to cross the village border.
I got injured while escaping
the goons who were after us.
I beg you.
Please save our girl!
Please save her.
What? Planning to retire from
your Robinhood duties?
No way! What's the matter?
We've misunderstood them.
They didn't stop helping us.
Hello?
It actually stopped because
they were in trouble.
When someone who helped us
faces hardship,
we must stand by them in support.
We'll support you.
A private jet has been booked
from Australia to India.
They're landing on the sixth.
I'll handle Google, and you handle them.
Sir, it's a confirmation call.
You're landing at 9:30
on the sixth morning.
9:32 am.
India's Number-One
Security Agency, right, sir?
Basically, VIPs like you
approach the agency.
India's Number-One Security Agency.
Yes!
Ram!
Do you still remember my small help?
You gave me a family when I had no one.
You looked after us the whole year,
though we only asked for a meal.
How can I forget, Grandpa?
Whoever helps us during
our hard times is equal to God.
If such a person is in trouble, one must
stand by them till the last breath.
You were with me for all these days.
Why didn't you tell me it was you?
Grandpa, as you once said,
"If I take credit,
the help becomes mine alone.
If I stay anonymous,
it becomes that of humanity."
You've lost enough.
You shouldn’t lose anything anymore.
That's why I brought your
granddaughter back here.
Hey, security.
Just like you have a backup,
even I have a backup.
I'm playing a movie
in the middle of the village.
Go watch it.
Once upon a time, there was
a village named Rudrakonda.
This is a Cannabis farm.
The villagers have become experts
in growing narcotic plants.
It's them who raise the crops,
and it's them who transport
the harvest illegally.
Do you know who's
the mastermind behind them?
Hey, security!
That oldie whom you think you've saved
and this village dependent on him
will all be destroyed by this one video.
To stop that from happening…
you should hand over the license
to me within 30 minutes.
My officers are waiting.
Run!
Robin, let's go.
This deal is important for him.
He definitely won't expose this video.
-In the meanwhile, I will somehow--
-Robin, please!
Please don't oppose me,
just this one time.
Let's go.
Hello?
You've come into my kingdom
and done all this…
I must definitely felicitate you today.
Come.
If you don't come,
I'll have to felicitate the villagers.
-Come.
-No, Ram.
Hey! Lord is my witness,
I don't know anything!
You fraud!
Just kill him.
If you let him off,
not just this one,
he won’t let any deal happen.
He'll devour us.
Hey! Are you saying
I can't make that deal with him around?
I'll make him close that deal for me.
When the deal gets done,
I'll felicitate both of you together.
Deena.
Security,
if you want that oldie, this village,
and the video to be safe,
you must personally
deliver the stuff safely.
I warned you that
any failure in the deal
with David would cost your lives.
The stuff didn't arrive on time.
Watch while each one of your heads
gets hacked.
What do you mean the stuff hasn't arrived?
The trucks started last night itself.
Only the trucks reached.
But the stuff hasn't.
David bhai has landed in India.
May your soul rest in peace.
-Hey, Muthu!
-Swami.
Where is Muthu?
I'm Muthu, Swami.
Azhaga!
-Azhaga!
-Swami.
He entrusted all the tasks to me
and left for Sri Lanka overnight, Swami.
Swami?
Swami!
Hey, Varada!
With the Lord as my witness!
Hey, Swami.
If you make a replacement, it’s art.
If I do the same, will it hurt you?
Shouldn't you be fair?
Come. Let's sit and talk.
You must've realized by now that
I can do anything with your stuff.
Quote a number that can stop me.
We'll close the deal.
How much do you want?
I asked Varada the same question,
the other day.
I didn't get any money,
but I'm satisfied I broke
your 30-year-old trust.
Isn't that when you started avoiding him?
Even if I keep him away,
he can't stay away from me.
Really?
Where?
Why isn't he beside you?
Your master plan was to
step into the international market,
hand over this entire village
and your men to David,
and settle in Dubai all by yourself.
When I told,
he and his gang ditched you
and left you here like an orphan.
Master plan?
I never had such a plan.
Of course, you don't have such a plan.
But I told them you did.
And they believed.
Those wretched fools!
They've been with me for 30 years.
How can they believe your words?
-I'll show them hell--
-Hey!
I was just joking.
They didn't believe me.
But you believed my words.
And you're supposed to be their leader.
If you believed the words of an outsider
like me, without thinking twice,
it's no surprise that
the people who work for you
believed me, Swami!
Aren't you getting the high?
Lord is my witness.
This is your stuff.
I hacked your phone
and stole your contacts.
With a wink, I provoked your ego
and made you
close that deal with me.
I pushed away everyone
who stood by you,
emptied your accounts,
and left you like an orphan
in the same village you orphaned!
Hey, Swami…
you learned about me
after I entered your life.
But I learned all about you
before entering your life.
I'm more dangerous than you.
Hey! Who the hell are you?
You brutally killed my father,
who was loyal to you.
Are you…
Perumal's son?
Or Dorai's son?
Sethu!
Hey, I joked again!
How could you believe
everything I speak?
After replacing all these people,
how would it be fair to let you go?
I replaced you, too.
Hey! Stop it!
If your strength lies in
weaving magic with words,
mine is taking lives with actions.
I don't need the stuff.
I just want to take your life!
For you to kill me,
you need to beat me first.
To beat me, you need to touch me first.
What is the use
of all your strength, Swami,
when you can't even touch me?
If you dare, come catch him, pal!
Touch him, and you go straight to coma
He's a wild warrior beyond measure
Do you even listen, Rama?
He climbs on your head like a storm
A tiny spark that shows you the stars
Cross him, and you're in for a ride
Thieves around here? Better stay silent
Fight the fierce swarm of bees
Like a stone carving fate
Why'd you hit me, buddy?
Look at this. I got a swelling!
Burning red, he’s a firestorm!
Yet, he asked you to kiss him!
Now you've scorched
Your mustache crisp!
Trapped like a fly
In Spider-Man’s web
Like an ant which stings
If you poke your finger in its nest!
If you dare, come catch him, pal!
Touch him, and you go straight to coma
He's a wild warrior beyond measure
Do you even listen, Rama?
He climbs on your head like a storm
A tiny spark that shows you the stars
Cross him, and you're in for a ride
Thieves around here? Better stay silent
Left, right, up, down
Like a washing machine gone wild!
Front, back, back to back
Spinning cool, breaking hard!
Inch by inch
Crushing like a sugarcane press!
No gaps, no maps
Rolling smooth like ice!
Like playing kabaddi
With raw electricity!
Robinhood’s own brand of chaos!
He stirs a storm in your mind
Waiting to explode!
Bye!
You've sealed my death
through the hand of the Lord I worship.
Check out what Premji
said about your Swami.
Varada! Don't believe Swami.
He arranged cameras without our knowledge.
He's planning to leave the country
after selling us to David bhai.
You're the only one who can save
me and our people, man.
I'll do whatever you say.
[In Tamil] What's bothering you, Swami?
Hey, police!
I'll pay you whatever you want.
Finish him off first.
Are you trying to buy me off
with the money you stole from the people?
Robinhood!
Robinhood?
Who's Robinhood?
I don't know what or how you'll do it.
I want my money back, and you
must get hold of that Robinhood.
Find out which accounts got money
from the minister's account.
Rama dootha Hanuman.
RH.
Rama dootha…
Robin.
Robinhood.
How could you reach Robinhood before me?
Family emotion is more significant
than all emotions.
It may be your job, sir.
But for me, this is a mission!
I'm not Robinhood, sir.
-Ram!
-Sir?
What will you say if I arrest you,
saying you are Robinhood?
I'm not Robinhood, sir.
Nobody can cheat Victor.
Who's Victor now?
I've been waiting for this day
for several years.
-That Robinhood--
-Sir.
Hey, he is not Robinhood.
Maybe it's not him.
You're right, sir.
If we reveal him as Robinhood,
he'll become a hero in society.
I don't want a goon to become a hero.
For the world outside,
he's not Robinhood.
-Will you speak to him?
-No need!
If we meet a thief like him,
people call us his partners.
-Anyway, you've done a great job.
-Thank you, sir.
That's why we call him a wild dog, sir.
Varada already told me about you…
that you're a big fraud!
You've changed both my name and place.
Who the hell is this Robinhood?
Can you bring tons of stuff here
without getting caught by the police?
David bhai?
You look fit.
But unfit for David!
-You're very addictive.
-Thank you.
But David hates addiction.
The deal time is 9 o'clock.
It's now 9:05.
Want to have it?
No!
The lollipops are red.
Enemies are dead.
It's a David's quote!
A demon became no one.
-Because of one man.
-Who's that, bhai?
ROBINHOOD!
He's not only there in your life,
but he's there in my life, too!
And wherever he is,
I'm the one who's going to take his life!
Who's Robinhood, sir?
God created all humans equally.
But the money created by humans
has brought about differences among us.
A heroic figure who fought
to erase inequality
and uphold human justice
-that's Robinhood.